# RAEVEN GONÇALVES



#### ASPIRING FRONT-END DEVELOPER

- Mirandela, Bragança
- +351 960214943
- raevengoncalves@gmail.com
- www.raeven-protfolio.vercel.app

Nationality: British | Residency: Portuguese |

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative, analytical and detailed orientated aspiring front-end developer eager to develop and grow front-end web developer skills. Although new to this field, I offer 15 years of experience in a variety of fields and a multitude of transferrable skills.

I am passionate about technology, innovation and programming. I have recently finished EPICODE'S front-end bootcamp in which I developed user-friendly interfaces using HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, React and Tailwind.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Independent Contractor**, 06/2018 - Current **Self Employed**, Mirandela, Portugal

Management of general construction and installation services.

# New Business Development Manager, 07/2010 - 01/2017

**ZD Marketing**, Johannesburg, South Africa

Obtained, managed, grew and maintained new and existing corporate clientele.

# Warehouse and Stores Manager, 06/2009 - 06/2010

Powermac, Johannesburg, South Africa

 Ran, managed and maintained the productivity and smooth running of the warehouse and stores, the staff and the stock.

Motor Technician, 08/2008 - 03/2009

Toyota, Johannesburg, South Africa

Repaired and inspected motor vehicles for services and/or with damage.

**Inventory Manager**, 01/2002 - 07/2008 **Matters Marketing**, Johannesburg, South Africa

• Responsible for all logistics, receiving of stock and the dispatching of orders for timeous delivery to customers.

# CORE SKILLS

- Front-end development
- Web-based software engineering
- Testing and maintenance
- HTML and XML
- JavaScript

- Website design
- Git
- React

#### **EDUCATION**

EPICODE, July 2022

# Front-End Web Developer

• Coursework in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, TypeScript, Agile methodologies, Heroku, Visioning (Git/GitHub), data structure and algorithms.

# FreeCodeCamp, February 2022

• Responsive Web Design

#### Codecademy, 2022

- React
- JavaScript

#### DataCamp, 2022

• Python Basic Fundamentals

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Negotiation
- Creativity
- Problem Solving
- Interest in lifelong learning